(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T23:35:54.808493",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日の3Dお披露目は…
Today's 3D showcase is...
ラオーラが3Dで初登場！
Raora makes her 3D debut!
チャッティーニランドにやってきたラオーラが...
Raora arrives at Chattini Land, and...
ジェットパックをかけてミニゲームで大暴れ！
Unleashes chaos in mini-games for a jetpack!
泣いて！
Crying!
Please give me the ticket!!
怒って！
Angry!
I'm done with this! I'm so done, I'm leaving!
セクシーなラオーラも見れちゃう！
You can even see a sexy Raora!
もちろん、歌も歌っちゃうよ！
Of course, she'll sing songs too!
先輩と喧嘩もしちゃって...
Even getting into fights with her seniors...
ジェットパックは手に入るのかな？
Will she get her hands on the jetpack?!
ラオーラ・パンテーラの3Dお披露目、はじまるよー！
Raora Panthera's 3D Showcase is starting!
Ciao Ra!
Are you recording me? Ah, where should I look? Where should I look?
What is this place?
Oh my gosh! That's a... That's a giant Chattino on the castle!
Oh my gosh! And look at the one on the fountain! All of them in 3D!
And there's another one over there! And another one over there!
Wait a second... Is this... Is this...
Is this Chattini Land?!
That's so cool!
Ah, hey, hey, cameraman! Come here, come here, come here!
How do I look in 3D, huh?
Hey, you should take a look to...
...my Chattino! Look at him! Isn't he 3D?
So cute, right?
Oh! And you also should take a look to my tail!
Big cat means big tail!
What do you think? How do I look?
Hey, Raora! Raora, Raora, Raora!
Woah! Ah!
Chattino! What did you do?
Come here now! I'm gonna... I'm gonna use my weapon!
Yeah, come here!
Now, how dare you! How dare you knock me over like this!
Wait a second!! I need to tell you something!
Huh? You can talk? Oh, that's impressive.
Well, I'm guessing... You need me for something? What do you need?
Yeah. There's this thing we want, but... The only way you can get it is by clearing all the Mini-Games here in Chattini Land!
Eh? Mini-games? Something you can only get here by clearing mini-games?
I think I know what it is.
It's... that thing over there!
Ah! I knew it! It's a jetpack!
All the Chattini want one so badly, right?
We can't get it on our own, though, so help us out Raora! Please!
Are you begging me?
Well, you know, little one... No.
I told you I'm not giving you the jetpack. So, I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
Please! Please! Pleeease!
Are you following me?
Well... I guess... It's a special day after all...
You know what? I'll give it a shot!
Yaaaaay!
Okay, then what should I do here?
The game's in this area of the land, so good luck!
Okay, then. You know what? I'm gonna do my very best!
Well, I should go then. Ganba-Raora! Rawr!
Oh, wait. The right way is over there.
I mean... I'm heading out! Ganba-Raora! Rawr!
この番組はご覧のスポンサーの提供でお送りいたします。
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん？
Are you really gonna act pure 'til you die?
Love, bluh bluh bluh
ラブと超ライク パーティションはない、ない
Love and super like, there's no partition, none
きみだけが 特別じゃないんだ
You're not the only special one
反省とか あたしに求められても...
Even if you ask me to reflect on myself...
ほんと 病んだり勘違いしないで
Seriously, don't get all depressed or misunderstand
で？ で？ で？
So? So? So?
どうしてなんで 期待の戸締まり忘れるの？
Why and how do you forget to lock away your expectations?
最初にあれほど やめときなって伝えたじゃん
I told you right from the start to stop doing that
お純情様、あちらが出口ですが...
Mr. Pure Heart, the exit is over there, but...
やっぱ 帰りたくない...ですか？
Do you... actually not want to go home?
ホップ ステップ う〜、ワンモアチャンス！
Hop, step, ooh... one more chance!
もうやっぱ アピってラビったらいいジャン
Seriously, if you appeal and go wild like a rabbit, it's fine
POPな愛撫 騙ったらいいジャン
If you fake pop affection, it's fine
みっともないから 嫉妬仕舞いな
It's embarrassing, so hide your jealousy
発火しちゃうとか くっそだせえな
Blowing up or whatever is so damn lame
淋しくなったら 誰でもいいジャン 埋まれればいいジャン
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get buried
嫌嫌愛して 生きたくなって 死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん？
Reluctantly loving, wanting to live, playing pure pure until you die?
やっぱ アピってラビったらいいジャン
Seriously, if you appeal and go wild like a rabbit, it's fine
BADなダンス 腫魔ったらいいジャン
If you dance badly and go crazy, it's fine
やっぱり 好きとかやってられんわ
Honestly, I can't keep dealing with "love" and stuff
馬鹿じゃない？ 嗚呼くっそ鬱陶しいわ
Are you stupid? Ah, so damn annoying
淋しくなったら 誰でもいいジャン 埋まれればいいジャン
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get buried
厭厭愛して 死にたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK？
Reluctantly loving, wanting to die, I'm wandering back and forth, OK?
「はーい」
"Okaay"
Love, bluh bluh bluh
バーストから インスタント・ラヴァー
From burst to instant lover
頭＋身体が ばかに絡まらぁ
Head + body stupidly entwined
ゴーストなら アンデッド・マナー
If you're a ghost, undead manners
嗚呼未だ淫ら 今は火花散らば
Ah, still lewd, now if sparks fly
それがアンサー・だ
That's the answer
バーストから インスタント・ラヴァー
From burst to instant lover
頭＋身体が ばかに絡まらぁ
Head + body stupidly entwined
ゴーストなら アンデッド・マナー
If you're a ghost, undead manners
嗚呼未だ淫ら 今は火花散らば
Ah, still lewd, now if sparks fly
それがアンサー・だ
That's the answer
う〜、ワンモアチャンス！
Ooh, one more chance!
もうやっぱ アピってラビったらいいジャン
Seriously, if you appeal and go wild like a rabbit, it's fine
POPな愛撫 騙ったらいいジャン
If you fake pop affection, it's fine
みっともないから 嫉妬仕舞いな
It's embarrassing, so hide your jealousy
発火しちゃうとか くっそだせえな
Blowing up or whatever is so damn lame
淋しくなったら 誰でもいいジャン 埋まれればいいジャン
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get buried
嫌嫌愛して 生きたくなって 死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん？
Reluctantly loving, wanting to live, playing pure pure until you die?
やっぱ アピってラビったらいいジャン
Seriously, if you appeal and go wild like a rabbit, it's fine
BADなダンス 腫魔ったらいいジャン
If you dance badly and go crazy, it's fine
やっぱり 好きとかやってられんわ
Honestly, I can't keep dealing with "love" and stuff
馬鹿じゃない？ 嗚呼くっそ鬱陶しいわ
Are you stupid? Ah, so damn annoying
淋しくなったら 誰でもいいジャン 埋まれればいいジャン
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get buried
厭厭愛して 死にたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK？
Reluctantly loving, wanting to die, I'm wandering back and forth, OK?
やっぱ アピってラビったらいいジャン
Seriously, if you appeal and go wild like a rabbit, it's fine
とっくのとうに 終わった思い出
Memories that ended long, long ago
みっともないとか 言ってごめんな
Sorry for saying it was embarrassing
発火したいけど もうダメなんだ
I want to spark up, but it's no use anymore
淋しくなったら 誰でもいいジャン 埋まれればいいジャン
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get buried
否否愛して 狂いたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK？
Reluctantly loving, wanting to go crazy, I'm wandering back and forth, OK?
「はーい」
"Okaay"
やややや 悪い子さん
Ya-ya-ya-ya, bad kid
まあまあまあまあ お愛顧じゃん
Well well well, favor us, won't you
さあさあさあさあ 始めるよ
Come on, come on, let me begin
もっと この穴を愛してよ
Love this hole even more
さあさあさあさあ 始めるよ もっと この穴を愛してよ
Come on, come on, let me begin, love this hole even more...
だっせ
So lame.
Ah! Look at this place!
I was not expecting to play a game in such a pretty place.
And I wonder what kind of game it's gonna be.
Hmm...
Raora...
This is your conscience.
Huh? My conscience? Do I have one?
Mori?
Yep. It's your turn.
Say something, say something!
Is that... Raora?
Is that a ghost? What is that?
Where is... I can't see anyone.
Raora!
Is that a dog?
Yay!
Congrats Raora on your 3D debut!
We're so happy for you!
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
Congratulations!
Thank you! You're cute!
No, you're cute! You're cute!
カワイイ！
So cute!
Thank you!
Well, as you may have assumed by our grand entrance over here,
your opponents for this mini-game are, as you see...
みなさん！Mori Calliope from hololive English -Myth-!
Everyone! Mori Calliope from hololive English -Myth-!
こんにちは、baby! This is Ouro Kronii from hololive English -Promise-!
Hello, baby! This is Ouro Kronii from hololive English -Promise-!
And look at this beautiful woman here. Who is this?
誰ですか？
Who is it?
あ、どっちこっち？あ、こっち！
Ah, which way, this way? Ah, this way!
指指！ホロライブゲーマーズから来ました犬神ころね、よろしくね！
Yubi yubi! From hololive GAMERS, I'm Inugami Korone! Nice to meet you!
よろしく！
Nice to meet you!
ころね先輩、初めまして！ 初めまして！
Korone-senpai, nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today!
日本語上手！ いえいえいえ...
Your Japanese is so good! No, no, no...
Thank you so much, Mori!
What kind of game are we gonna play today?
Well, get ready, because it's time for...
1, 2, 3, Say Cheese!
All right. Now then...
Here are the rules. Chattini are going to jump out of the bushes at random intervals to snap a photo of you.
And when they do so, you've got to enter the frame and then strike a specific pose for them.
Okay, okay. Sounds easy.
Like that, like that. Just move into the camera frame...
...and strike the pose once the Chattini jump out.
Wait, wait.
That is a good example! Yeah, exactly!
She's a little too hyped for that. - I know!
Pretty hot!
No no no, you have to be competitive. You have to be competitive in this game, yes.
And well, as you have seen, Raora clears if she can pose five or more times at the designated location within the time limit.
Super easy, right? - I got it!
It sounds super fun! Let's go!
Yeah, but it's not going to be easy. - Yeah, it's not going to be easy because...
...we're going to be taking part as well...
...and I'm going to get in your way!
No, no! All up in your business!
I'm going to get in your way!
Well, whatever you think...
I'm going to get the ticket! I'm going to win!
No! - Yes! - I guess that means we're all going to get...
...super close! - Loser! Raora loser!
No, I'm not a loser! You're a loser!
No no no! - Woah, I feel like I'm really confident now! - No, you are!
A little too confident. No, don't worry, no, it's okay, it's all good, it's all good.
Let's strike a pose, it's a pose game. - It's a pose game!
Okay, okay. Are you guys excited?
I'm excited! - Okay, if everybody's ready then...
Let's do this!
Let me do it!
Hope you're all ready, troops! Are you guys excited? - Yeah!
Get ready to start voguing. Since it would be a shame to go straight into the real thing, let us do some practice first, okay?
Okay, okay, let me do it.
All right. So, here we go. 3, 2, 1, start!
Okay, let's see. First camera...
Here, here! Hey hey hey!
No, no, no!
What is that? - Yo, yo, yo! - No no no!
Okay, let's see next camera. - Yes, yes!
This is Calliope's time to shine!
Okay, where to? One more!
Hey hey hey!
Oh... where, where, where?
No, no, no!
Wait!
You doing okay there, buddy? - I'm so good!
I will touch you, and I will hurt you. Just so we're all on the same page, I will hurt you if I have to.
Hurt me? I love it! I love that!
That's not the response I expected. - I'm fine with it!
Well, shall we move on to the main event, ladies? - Okay! Yes!
Okay, the time limit for the main event is two minutes. Whoever strikes the right pose in the required spots most is the winner.
Now then... Let's get this show on the road! 3, 2, 1, it's on!
Okay... Where is it?
Yeah!
That was kind of nutty!
Let's go, let's go! What is it?
No no no no no!
Did you get it?
Oh man, I'm going to get injured! - Yo yo yo!
No! Wait, you hurt me!
Okay, dang it! Next one is mine! What do you think?
As I said, I will hurt you. - No, nonono!
Man, everyone's so good... - I know! - ...at, you know, hurting each other.
Dang it!
Where is it? - No no no no!
Why is she so strong?
She's rejecting all of my pushes!
Okay... Oh, man.
They're really blocking...
Man, I'm not even gonna try on this one.
All right. Next.
Well, they're all squabbling.
Calliope takes the lead!
That's so tiring...
No! Not every time! You can't get it every time, Kronii!
Come on!
Let me have this one!
おいおいおい！ That's so tiring!
Oi, oi, oi! That's so tiring!
Yo, why are y'all so strong?
I don't get it.
Are you good?
We are good.
Okay, so good.
Man, I feel like we just had a... battle.
Raora! I'm good!
That's what I call いい勝負。
That's what I call a good match.
Okay. How was it?
How do you guys think you did?
I think I won!
I think Kronii won.
No, no, no...
With the sheer force of her muscles pushing people out of the way!
And it wasn't even that! She could not... I mean, hey, competitive spirit! I can't even argue with that.
Well then! Well done, everyone!
Well, let's see how that weighs up against the results, shall we?
I bet I am the winner!
No, no, no, Raora, no, no, no...
Yes, Raora! Yes, I am the winner!
All right, all right. Let's see how we all did then. Here we go. Drum roll, please.
Winner is...
The winner is...
Kronii!
That crazy clock, she's so strong! Man, congrats!
Thank you, thank you.
I did good anyway!
There was no defeating the Clock of Steel. Oh, man.
It's rigged! It's rigged!
She's too good, Raora. She can't be beaten. I tried to pick her up and move her, she just can't be moved. She's immovable!
Man, it's really too bad though. I was gonna give you the ticket if you managed to win, but oh well. Round of applause. Boo-hoo, so sad. Oh, I cry!
Wait, Mori, wait a second! There must be a way, right? I need the ticket! I need to clear all the games!
It's not up to me, but... what to do, what to do? I feel kind of bad, you're my cute kohai.
Korone先輩どうすればいい？
Korone-senpai, what should I do?
そうね、Do you like Japanese TV show?
Yeah, well... Do you like Japanese TV shows?
Yes, I love Japanese TV show, yes!
Yes, I love Japanese TV shows!
Please, cute, おねだり！
Please, cute, onedari! (begging)
おねだり？ Cute begging? You want me to beg?
Onedari? Cute begging? You want me to beg?
Yeah, おねだり！ This camera, okay? This camera.
Yeah, onedari! This camera, okay? This camera.
Get kind of low.
Up, up eyes, up eyes, okay?
Cute face, okay?
I can't wait.
Cute おねだり！
Cute begging!
3, 2, 1, action!
Please! Please, Korone先輩！ Please, おねだり！
Please! Please, Korone-senpai! Please, onedari!
Please, give me the ticket! Please, I need the ticket! Please, Korone先輩, please!
Please, give me the ticket! Please, I need the ticket! Please, Korone-senpai, please!
Please! Give me the ticket!
Oh man, I feel so bad now!
I need the ticket!
ここまでやるとは！
I didn't think she'd go this far!
Since you've done... そんなほしいのね！
Since you've done... You really want it that much!
All right, all right, Raora! You've done it! Look at your hand, look at your hand!
[On-Screen Text: Got the Ticket!!] やった！
[On-Screen Text: Got the Ticket!!] Yay!
Cute おねだり！
Cute begging!
I got the ticket! Let's go!
Well done. See, no problem. Happy ending.
You will receive the Jetpack Chattini if you gather up three tickets. Count 'em, three! So good luck on the next games as well!
Thank you, senpais! Thank you!
Now go do your best! - Okay, I'll do my best! Thank you so much!
Go slay! - I'll go slay!
Wait, go straight!
Go straight! This way, this way! Go straight!
Let's go!
Bye! Bye-bye! See ya!
Chattini Land - Jungle Area
Oh my gosh, this area is really different from the last one.
It's super dark. And what's with all the bars?
It's... it's kind of scary.
Hold on... What is that?
I hear voices! Is... is it ghosts?
What is that?
Oh my gosh! These guys...
Please! My time has come! Please take my soul!
Are those ghosts? Or... is that Nerissa and Moona?
Yeah, you're gonna say you don't recognize us?
Of course I recognize you!
Hello!
Congratulations on your 3D!
Yay! Thank you!
Finally!
Thank you!
I think we have to introduce...
Starting from me?
Hello everyone! I am Moona Hoshinova from hololive Indonesia Generation 1!
Hi darlings! This is hololive English -Advent-'s devilish diva, the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft!
Thank you for having me!
Thank you so much for being here!
We came here to bring a game for you.
A game?!
It involves cooperation!
Oh, awesome! That's good!
What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do?
Well, the game this time is...
One, two, three... Limbo Dance! Panthera!!
Limbo Dance! Panthera!!
The rules are super simple.
The three of us are gonna do some sexy limbo dance...
dancing, yes, the limbo dance dancing as we make our way towards the stage!
So exciting!
Me too! And once we're there, there's one thing left to do.
We're all gonna sing a super awesome trio song!
So happy!
Sounds simple, right? / It sounds simple, let's see.
I am... I'm born for this! Let's go!
But, you know, are we really gonna be able to do this? I think we might have not thought ahead too far.
Of course we're gonna do it!
No, but, you know, we all have something that I feel like will make limbo a little bit difficult.
Oh, don't worry, Nerissa.
Something that is really, really hard, but it's fine!
Save it for the game, ladies!
Let's do it!
First off, though, we need to do some warm-up.
Oh!
Yeah! Keep going, girls!
Yeah! Let's warm up a little bit for the game now!
CAN THEY CLEAR IT?!
All right, let's get ready! All together!
I took off my jacket because it's so hot in here!
Can you do me a favor? / Of course!
Could you jump a little bit more? Just a little bit.
Yes! Why not?!
I love jumping, so let's go!
And look at those shoulders, too! Show those off! Very nice!
Thank you!
Oh my god, I'm gonna do my very best in limbo dance!
Let's do it then!
Get the music going!
GAME START!
Nice music! Do you hear that?
Are you ready? / I'm ready!
It's your 3D debut, so get going!
Well, that's super easy for me! Are you guys ready?
Yes! / Okay, here we go!
Off you go!
I'm going next!
Moona!
It's easy for her!
Yes! Nerissa! You can do it! Oh my goodness!
Easy-peasy!
Who's next? Who's next?
Same order, let's keep it going.
That's a little bit unfair. Well, I'm gonna do it then!
Show us how it's done!
Good job!
I can do it!
Easy, easy! / Look at you go!
Nerissa! Nerissa!
Easy game!
This one's a little bit more difficult!
Maybe senpai order?
Senpai, over there!
I can do it for you guys.
Okay.
Oh...
Oh, look at her! Look at her go!
Next up... your turn, Eli.
Watch how it's done.
Show me clean!
Woo! That's so clean, girl!
Let's go! My turn!
Definitely gonna do it!
Come on, kouhai!
So good!
Okay, maybe switch it off, I'll go first.
Yes, you go first.
Oh my goodness!
She's nailing it! Are you gonna be able to do it, Moona?
You can do it.
I believe I can do it.
This is a really tough one.
You can do it!
Yeah! She did it!
All right. My turn! Let me show you off my skills!
You can do it, Raora!
Oh good, I'm good, I'm good. You're okay, you're okay.
Got it, got it, got it!
No, we have to keep going! There's still two more!
All right. Back, right...
Let me rest a little bit. Oh my god.
I'm too old for this.
Come here, grandma. Come here.
You have no idea of modern games!
Two more, two more! Come on, come on! Let's go!
We have two more to go, right?
Wait a second... you dropped yours!
Oh no!
Well, I think I'm done with these two then!
Oh, go for it!
I think I still can keep it for now.
Time to get serious. So, I'm gonna lock in.
This is impossible, hello?
Yeah, it's a little bit low, but I think we can do it.
Okay. I'll try first.
She's too good, Moona! I don't know if we can do it!
Oh my god. Okay. Come on, you can do it.
You can do it. Come on, Moona, Moona, Moona...
No, I think I have an idea.
She got an idea!
That's a great idea! The power of brand-new legs!
Let me see. You can do it!
Come on, Raora, you got this! Okay...
I think I can do it...
Ta-da! That's great!
That's really nice.
Okay, I don't think I can... I don't know if I can do this one.
I mean, you did so good so far! You can do it! Do your best!
I think I'm too tall for this one.
I'm gonna hold you. I'm gonna fall, I'm gonna fall.
I'm gonna hold you, I'm gonna hold you!
Yeah! I did it!
I'm going to follow her way! I'm going to follow her way!
Yes! Let's do this!
Moona... where is she gonna put it?
Now she's getting serious! She's getting serious!
Yeah!
Okay, okay. Then, it's my turn now. What to do...
Well, I'm a big cat, so...
Meow...
Nyan nyan nyan nyan! Move it!
Thank you! Here I go!
Well, I still think we have one more obstacle yet before us.
Wait, wait, wait... Look at the slope!
Let me see! We've got to go up!
All right, everyone! Time for our limbo dance.
Oh yeah, limbo dance now! Yes!
Let's go to the stage!
Are you guys excited? So excited! I am so ready!
Oh my god, that was so tiring! Yeah, but we did it!
We're on the stage already! Yeah, we're here!
You're right! Here!
So ready for this! Okay!
I don't know what I'm doing, but let me do it! We gotta go full-on!
Yeah! All right!
Last part!
捕まえちゃう！ (どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ)
I'll catch you! (Where are you? No way, no way, wherever you are, no way!)
捕まえちゃう！ (だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ わたし以外はダメよ)
I'll catch you! (Who are you with? No way, no way, anyone but me is no way!)
甘いよ甘い そんな装備じゃ
You're naive, so naive; with gear like that,
逃げられるわけ無いじゃないか
there's no way you can escape!
狙いをつけて 密かに背後から
I'll take aim quietly from behind...
I love you
私のことを好きになるはず
you're bound to fall for me.
I love you
そこに正義があるの
that's where justice lies!
何度言わせるつもりなの？ おやおや
How many times do I have to say it? Oh dear!
抵抗するならしてごらん！ いないと
Try resisting if you want! Surprising...
我が儘だと知ってるけれど
I know I'm being selfish,
私の方が上手なようね
but I guess I'm just better at this.
冷たい言葉 優しい視線
Cold words, a gentle gaze...
獲物は… 君だよ！
My prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere!
君の 君の 心 盗んでみせるよ
Your, your heart—I'll steal it!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere!
君の 君の 心を離さない
Your, your heart—I'll never let it go!
熱いよ熱い 愛のルールは
So intense, so intense! The rules of love...
破られるため在るんだよ
exist to be broken!
ずるい罠へと 誘う微笑みは
The smile inviting you into my sly trap...
I miss you
好きのせいだし悪くないでしょ
it's because I like you, so it's not bad, right?
I miss you
それが重度の恋よ
that's a serious case of love.
絶対全てをいただくよ？ おやおや
I'm going to take everything, okay? Oh dear!
反抗するならしてごらん！ てごわい
Try fighting back if you want! Tough, aren't you?
偽りだって疑うよりも
Rather than doubting it as fake,
私の事信じてみてよ
try believing in me.
優しい言葉 冷たい視線
Kind words, a cold gaze...
獲物は… 君だよ！
My prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 君の瞳が欲しい
Cutie Panther, I want your eyes!
私 きっと きっと 盗んでみせるよ
I will definitely, definitely steal them!
Cutie Panther 君の瞳が欲しい
Cutie Panther, I want your eyes!
私 きっと 素早く逃がさない
I will definitely, quickly, never let you escape!
何度言わせるつもりなの？ おやおや
How many times do I have to say it? Oh dear!
抵抗するならしてごらん！ いないと
Try resisting if you want! Surprising...
我が儘だと知ってるけれど
I know I'm being selfish,
私の方が上手なようね
but I guess I'm just better at this.
冷たい言葉 優しい視線
Cold words, a gentle gaze...
獲物は… 君だよ！
My prey is... you!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere!
君の 君の 心 盗んでみせるよ
Your, your heart—I'll steal it!
Cutie Panther 私 どこでも行くよ
Cutie Panther, I'll go anywhere!
君の 君の 心を離さない
Your, your heart—I'll never let it go!
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ
Where are you? No way, no way, wherever you are, no way!
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ わたし以外はダメよ
Who are you with? No, no, anyone other than me is a no-no!
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ
Where are you? No way, no way, wherever you are, no way!
捕まえちゃう！
I'll catch you!
だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ わたし以外はダメよ
Who are you with? No, no, anyone other than me is a no-no!
How was that, Velvet?
That's really nice!
That's how Velvet does it!
So cool, right?
So cool together! Nice!
Thank you for dancing and singing with me!
Ooh, and also...
Since we already finished...
...our session, so here's your...
...ticket!
Oh my god! I got it! Look at you!
Congratulations, Raora!
That's... one more left now!
That's all! Thank you so much, I'm so happy!
It was so fun, thank you for having us!
Thank you!
Good luck getting that final ticket too, all right?
We'll pull through!
I'll try for it.
I'll do my best.
I promise.
Thank you, girls!
You can do it!
Well, as for us, we should take our leave.
Bye-bye.
We must leave you.
Don't leave me, girls!
We need to go.
No! No! Oh...
They limbo danced so hard...
...that it became their default walking state.
Chattini Land Sci-Fi
Whoa! What is this place?
Oh my god, it seems like...
...this place came out of a science fiction movie or something like that.
But now I'm curious.
What kind of game did they got prepared for me this time?
Eh? What is that? What is this?
Wait... Wait a second.
I smell something... dog smell!
I know who you are! Come out!
Come here!
Bau Bau!
Aw, come here, come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
They're there! They were there!
Jeez! Surprise!
It's Biboo!
Ah, I'm so excited! I'm so nervous! I'm so happy!
Your tail's looking really happy, too!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Okay, let's talk about it.
There's a game to the right! And there's another game right here!
Okay, okay.
Well, why don't you guys introduce yourselves?
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
Together we are...
FUWAMOCO! Bau Bau!
And I'm not FUWAMOCO! Nor Bau Bau!
I'm Koseki Bijou, sparkling gem of hololive English -Advent-!
Koseki!
And then... Raora!
It's still me, Raora Panthera from hololive English -Justice-! This time in 3D!
Wait, have you introduced yourself before?
I'm not sure about that. Maybe?
It's always good for hello...
...intro!
So, what's the last game going to be?
Well, for this next game...
Actually...
You're the only one in this challenge!
What do you mean?
But we have a very important role, too, right?
We're going to... stop you!
No, no, no! You guys got to let me win!
We're going to be obstacles!
No, no, no! You got to let me win! It's my 3D debut, and it's the last ticket! I need it!
We're going to put you through the ringer! Yeah!
Are you ready to hear what the third and final game is? It is...
1, 2, 3! Run! Run! Raora!!
Okay, okay. What are the rules?
Okay, are you curious?
Take a look at the conveyor belt behind you!
Ooh! What is this, huh? There's nothing on it, Biboo.
Oh, hopefully hear me. There is something on it. Bring it out!
What is that? Ew! What is...
Pineapple pizza?!
Broken up spaghetti?! Ew! You know I can't take this!
Ketchup spaghetti?!
I'm done with this! I'm so done with this! I'm leaving! I'm leaving!
I'm not going to play this game!
No, I'm not going to play this game! It's too much for me!
No, no, no, no! It's too much for me! I'm done with this!
Well, do you notice that everything we brought out here is everything you hate?
Do you hate me? Why would you do this to me?
That's right, Raora! You're going to have to hop onto that thing and...
...and avoid everything that's on it!
You can do it! Do it, do it!
Wait a second, why are you guys here then?
What are you guys gonna do?
Well...
We'll be using certain... things...
...to make life more difficult for Raora!
No, no, no! You can't do this to me!
Yeah, you know, you really are a criminal!
Stop now! No, you're not gonna do this to me!
Well, let me go grab them!
Yeah, yeah, okay! We'll be right back!
No, no, no! Come back!
Hey! What are they gonna do?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Raora!
No, no, no, no, no! Okay, okay!
I'll play the game! I'll play the game! Okay!
You have to play the game! You have to play the game!
Okay, I'll play the game!
Did you like that? 'Cause there's more where that came from!
No, look at that with the onion!
It's bigger than you, Biboo!
What is that supposed to mean?! I'm bigger than this onion!
This is not a normal-sized onion!
Cucumbers are good for you! Yum!
Now then, let's get going here!
Let me go!
Alright, let me go!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine!
Raora's Fate?!
[Title: Raora's Fate?!]
Okay! Are you ready, Raora?
Um, I'm not so sure...
Ah, hey guys, guys, guys! Can we play another game?
Okay! The time limit...
You have to keep dodging for 60 seconds to level up, okay?
Okay, okay, okay, I'm ready.
There's a total of 3 levels!
So try to escape to the very end without getting hit, okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay then!
GAME START!
I'll do my best!
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no!
The onion! We can talk about it!
Okay, okay!
No, no, no, no! Email us...
Not the broken spaghetti!
Get away!
Oh my god!
No, no, no, no, no!
Slow down!
Big ball! Big ball!
NOOOOO!
FAILED! You failed!
Do you want to try again?
One more time?
Last time!
Level 1 Revenge!
[Title: Level 1 Revenge!]
How are you feeling?
Maybe we were a bit too hard on her. That was like a long time.
That's not fair...
Okay then...
We're gonna set the clock to 30 seconds. Does that sound more fair?
Okay, let's do it then!
I can definitely make it!
Okay, we're gonna go again!
3, 2, 1...
GAME START!
I'm running, I'm running!
No, no, no! Tell me...
You're doing good! Easy, easy!
No, no, no, no, no!
It's moving so fast!
CLEAR!
Level 1 CLEAR!
You did it!
That's a good deal!
You think you can go all the way?
That was just Level 1, you have Level 2 now!
That was too easy, you know!
Let me try Level 2 then!
You can do it!
It's my first time!
Level 2!
GAME START!
No, no, no, no, no!
You can do it! You have time!
Clear! Level 2 clear!
I did level 2 clear!
I cleared Level 2!
Well, you know, it was pretty easy.
Not falling down or anything, huh?
Well, maybe you didn't put enough effort...
Okay, well, we're gonna make it harder then! Get ready for...
Level 3!
This is the last one! The sticker is mine!
Here we go to the next level!
I think this one's gonna be extra hard!
Because you said that we weren't trying hard, you know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna make this one... You only have one try!
Oh, come on!
And you know what? That's not all! It's gonna be extra hard!
This is really not fair at all!
You guys are cheating! This is not fair!
You are so evil!
Level 3!
Game start!
Failed!
I don't think she's gonna be able to come back from that.
It's over! Bye-bye!
Yoshi yoshi, it's okay!
There, there, it's okay!
Yoshi yoshi yoshi...
There, there, there...
Well, you know, guys... Today is my 3D debut, right?
So maybe, you know, senpais... You guys could give me the sticker anyway?
No.
No! No! No!
You're so mean!
I'm not getting the sticker?!
No sticker for you! Sorry!
But Raora, we have prepared a special stage for you!
Ah, really?!
Well, while it was fun torturing you with things you hate...
We kind of want to see your cool side!
My cool side?
Yeah, your cool side! Show it off to everyone!
Maybe you can put all those angry feelings into the next song!
Yeah, sing!
Okay!
Go, go, go, go, go!
恋は戦争
Love is War
もう行き場がないわ
There's nowhere for it to go anymore
この恋の熱量
The heat of this love
灰色の雲
The grey clouds
モノクロの喧騒
The monochrome clamor
日差しはかげり
The sunlight casts a shadow
夕暮れは色を変えていく
The twilight changes color
嗚呼 世界がにじんで
Ah, the world blurs
それでも好きでいられるかなんて
Even so, can I keep loving you?
わかってる けどどうすればいいの
I know, but what should I do?
どうしたら どうすれば
What can I do? What should I do?
バカだな わたし...
I'm such a fool...
始めるのよ これは戦争
I'm starting this—it's war!
嬉しそうなキミをみるなんて
Seeing you look so happy...
切なる恋 それは罪
An earnest love, that is a sin
見せてあげる わたしの想いを
I'll show you my feelings
叫んでみたメガホンは壊れてたの
The megaphone I tried shouting into was broken
どれだけ背伸びしたって 君の視界に入らない
No matter how much I stand on tiptoe, I don't enter your sight
嗚呼 いつの間にか晴れた空
Ah, before I knew it, the sky cleared up
全然似合わない
It doesn't suit me at all
気持ちが抑えられなくて
I can't suppress my feelings
どうしたら どうすれば
What can I do? What should I do?
泣いてなんか ないんだからね
It's not like I'm crying or anything
大好き
I love you
たたかうのよ ハートを撃て
I will fight! Shoot for the heart!
手段なんて選んでられない
I can't afford to choose my means
スカート ひらり 見せつけるのよ
With a flutter of my skirt, I'll show off
君の視線 奪ってみせるの
I'll steal your gaze away
迎撃用意
Prepare for counterattack
戦況は未だ不利なのです
The battle situation is still unfavorable
恋は盲目
Love is blind
君の口づけで目が覚めるの！
Your kiss will awaken me!
Ah...
I'm sorry, Chattini!
I tried my best, but I only got two!
Noooo... my jetpack...
The jetpack exploded!
I'm sorry, Chattini...
Actually, I have a present for all of you!
Present? I wonder what it is. Is it a cucumber?
Uh-uh, let me tell you.
That's the best! It's not a jetpack, but it's really nice!
Thanks, Chattini!
Well then, before I reveal the best present ever, I've got an announcement to make!
Tada!
Raora pencil case & keychain!
Yes! This is a cute pencil case with me in a Chattino costume!
So I hope you guys can bring it everywhere: at school, in the office...
...literally everywhere! So please don't miss out, okay?
That was such a fun 3D showcase with a lot of things happening!
Did everyone have fun? Chattini, did you guys have fun?
Thank you! I'm so happy to hear that!
Thank you! Seems like you guys had a great time with me today. I'm so happy, thank you!
I'll keep doing my best to bring fun streams and more 3D live performances like this one today, okay?
I appreciate you guys so much. Thank you, Chattini, for all your support! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Finally!
It's the long-awaited present from me to everyone!
Are you guys ready? The present is...
my first original song!
Ah, I'm so happy!
It's full of things I like, and so many personal touches!
I worked really, really hard on this song, so I hope you guys are gonna take a listen to it, okay?
Are you guys ready? Are you guys excited?
Let's go to the stage!
Gacha × Gacha ADVENTURE!
(はい！ はい！ はい！ Pon! Pon!)
(Yes! Yes! Yes! Pon! Pon!)
(Gacha, Gacha, RAOOOOO!!)
さあ、さあ、お宝探しだ
Come on, come on, it's treasure hunting time!
「今日は、ど〜んな獲物が見つかるかにゃ？」
"I wonder what kind of prey we'll find today, nya?"
ほら、ほら、みんなも一緒に
Look, look, everyone together,
「楽しい冒険、しゅっぱ〜つ！」
"Off to an exciting adventure~!"
(Un! Due! Tre!)
ハマっちゃったら抜け出せないの〜
Once you get hooked, you can't get out~
食べ物ぬいぐるみ PizzaもPastaも全部
Food plushies, pizza, pasta, all of it,
詰め込んだ魅惑の迷宮 ワクワク止まらない
packed into an alluring maze, excitement won't stop!
(Proviamo!)
取れそうで取れなくてイライラ
It looks like I can get it, but I can't, so frustrating!
クレーンゲーム
Crane game,
「にゃ〜もう！」
"Nya~ jeez!"
諦めたままリタイアするはずないじゃない！
There's no way I'm giving up and retiring!
「目指せコンプリート！」
"Aiming for complete!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ♪
Now, one more time! Stopping me is useless♪
もう一回 繰り返すデジャブ
One more time, repeating déjà vu,
諦めろって言わないで
don't tell me to give up!
三度目の正直
Third time's the charm,
だから無問題 溢れる想いがとめらんない これって天職！？
so no problem! Overflowing feelings can't be stopped, is this my calling?!
楽しいことで満ちてる この先もずっと
Filled with fun things, from now on and forever!
「はい、せーのっ」
"Okay, ready, go!"
Gacha × Gacha ADVENTURE!
(ガチャ... ガチャ... ガチャ... ガチャ...)
(Gacha... Gacha... Gacha... Gacha...)
「ゲーム、リスタートー！」
"Game, restart~!"
グルグル回しまくっちゃえ
Spin it round and round!
「ダメだ... 止まらない！」
"Oh no... It won't stop!"
お目当ての獲物が出るまで
Until the target prey comes out,
「お願い... もう一回！」
"Please... one more time!"
(Bim bum bam!)
ビートに乗ったら止まれないの〜
Once I ride the beat, I can't stop~
音ゲーもお手製のもの
Rhythm games are easy peasy,
ComboもFeverも全部 キメタラ完璧 Groove!
Combo, Fever, everything, nail it all for a perfect Groove!
ズレたらゲームオーバーさ
If you slip, it's game over!
(Andiamo!)
レースゲーム エンジン全開で アチアチ
Racing game, full engine throttle, super hot,
白熱バトル！
a heated battle!
「いけいけ Go! Go! Go!」
"Go go Go! Go! Go!"
コーナーで差をつけたら
If you pull ahead at the corner,
目指すは1位だー！
aim for 1st place~!
さあ、もう一回 でも今日は終わり
Come on, one more time... but today is over,
もう一回 言いかけて止まる
one more time, I start to say it and stop,
楽しかった気持ちが 胸をキュッとするの
these fun feelings make my heart tighten.
ねぇねぇ、もうバイバイしなきゃダメ？
Hey hey, do we really have to say bye-bye?
まだ帰りたくない これって恋かな！？
I don't want to go home yet, is this love?!
ワクワクで満ち溢れた この先の日々も
Full of excitement, all the days ahead as well,
「一緒に冒険しよう！」
"Let me go on an adventure together!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ♪
Now, one more time! Stopping me is useless♪
もう一回 繰り返すデジャブ
One more time, repeating déjà vu,
諦めろって言わないで
don't tell me to give up!
何度でもチャレンジ
Challenge as many times as it takes!
だから無問題 溢れる想いが とめらんない これぞ天職！！
So no problem! Overflowing feelings can't be stopped, this is my true calling!!
何度でもやり直せる
You can restart as many times as you want,
そう人生は
that's right, life is—
(みんなも一緒に！)
(Everyone together!)
Gacha × Gacha ADVENTURE!
(はい！ はい！ はい！ Pon! Pon!)
(Yes! Yes! Yes! Pon! Pon!)
(Gacha, Gacha, RAOOOOO!!)
「また一緒に冒険しようね！ Ciao ciao♪」
"Let's go on an adventure together again! Ciao ciao♪"
That was so much fun!
How did you like it, Chattini? Did you like it?
Thank you for watching and listening!
Today was so much fun! Thank you so much everyone for all your support!
Thank you, Chattini, thank you!
I can't wait to see you all again!
Until next time, ciao ciao!
Raoooo~!
BIG CAT MEANS...
BIG DREAMS!